(SOFT ROCK BALLAD
PLAYING ON CAR STEREO)
(LAUGHING SOFTLY)
Mmm.
Hey! Start the car!
Start the car!
Dopinder,
start the fucking car!
Ahh!
-Whoo!
-Oh, I shit my pants.
Actually, that may
have been me.
-You're living the dreams, DP.
-Yeah.
-Devil-may-care attitude.
-(CHUCKLES)
Strong thighs.
Beautiful girlfriend.
Sorry I'm late.
I was rounding up
all the gluten in the world
and launching it in space
where it can't not hurt us
ever again.
Kiss me like you miss me, Red.
What in the fucksickle
is this?
My name's Cable,
I'm here for the kid.
What? The kid?
Move or die.
Kids give us a chance to be
better than we used to be.
He needs you.
You're a lot smarter
than I look.
(CHUCKLES)
I ain't letting
Cable kill this kid.
But I can't do this alone.
-Boop.
-Can you speak up?
It's hard to hear you with
that pity dick in your mouth.
We're going to form
a super-duper fuckin' group.
We need them tough,
morally flexible
and young enough
to carry their own franchise
for 10 to 12 years.
We will be known as
X-Force.
Isn't that
a little derivative?
You're absolutely right.
Now let's go get our fuck on.
(RAP MUSIC PLAYING)
Tell me they got that
in slow motion.
Doing the right thing
is messy.
But if you want to fight
for what's right,
sometimes you have
to fight dirty.
And that is why Sisterhood
of the Traveling Pants
-is pure pornography.
-Huh.
God, I wish
I finished college.
It lives up to the hype,
plus, plus.
Fuck it, they probably won't
even make a three.
Yeah, why would they?
Stop at two. You killed it.
-(WEASEL CHUCKLES)
-(LAUGHS)